<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PhotoStudio</string>
    <string name="solo_package_subtitle">A 20-minute session for 1 person, ideal for individual portraits or headshots.</string>
    <string name="pair_package_subtitle">A 30-minute session for 2 people, perfect for couples or friends. Includes 10 enhanced photos and 1 backdrop.</string>
    <string name="group_package_subtitle">A 30-minute session for 3-5 people, great for families or small groups. Includes 10 enhanced photos and 1 backdrop.</string>
    <string name="solo_package_description">₱500 - A 20-minute session for 1 person, ideal for individual portraits or headshots. Includes 5 enhanced photos and 1 backdrop.</string>
    <string name="pair_package_description">₱700 - A 30-minute session for 2 people, perfect for couples or friends. Includes 10 enhanced photos and 1 backdrop.</string>
    <string name="group_package_description">₱1000 - A 30-minute session for 3-5 people, great for families or small groups. Includes 10 enhanced photos and 1 backdrop.</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="continue_with_google">Continue with Google</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="login">LOGIN</string>
    <string name="or">or</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="don_t_have_an_account_register_here">Don\'t have an account? Register here</string>
    <string name="welcome_to_ncaptured_by_k">WELCOME TO\nCAPTURED BY K</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_text">
Studio Shoot Appointment Guidelines:
Studio shoot is strictly by appointment only.
We are open from 9am to 6pm.
We are located at 102 Purok 2, Batang, Ligao City.
Each booked slot will have unlimited shots but the number of photos to be released depends on your package.
Preparation / Doing make-up in the studio IS NOT ALLOWED.
Choosing of photos shall only be within 20 minutes.
The soft copy of the enhanced photos in the packages shall be given through a Google Drive link.
NO PRINT OUT.
Photos shall be released to the client and posted on our FB page WITHIN THE DAY OR THE DAY AFTER EACH SESSION.
Additional photo to be released within the day or the day after each session is 50php per shot.

-----------------------------------------------------------------

Welcome to [Captured by KI]! These Terms and Conditions outline the rules and regulations for using our mobile application "Captured by KI".
By accessing or using the App, you agree to comply with these Terms. If you do not accept, please refrain from using the App.

1. Acceptance of Terms
By creating an account, booking, or rebooking through the App, you agree to these Terms and our Privacy Policy.

2. Account Registration
- You may create an account using an email and password or sign in through Google.
- You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account.
- We reserve the right to suspend or terminate accounts that violate our policies.

3. Booking and Rebooking
- The App allows users to book and rebook photo sessions with our studio.
- All bookings are subject to availability and confirmation.
- Cancellations and rescheduling must comply with our cancellation policy.

4. Payments and Fees
- If applicable, payment details will be provided before booking.
- Any applicable taxes or fees will be disclosed before confirming a booking.

5. User Responsibilities
- You agree to provide accurate and truthful information.
- Any misuse of the App, including fraudulent bookings, may result in account suspension.

6. Privacy Policy
- We collect and process personal data in accordance with our Privacy Policy.
- Your data will only be used to manage bookings and enhance user experience.

7. Modifications to Terms
- We reserve the right to update these Terms at any time.
- Continued use of the App after changes indicates acceptance of the updated Terms.

8. Limitation of Liability
- We are not responsible for technical issues, service disruptions, or third-party actions.
- Our liability is limited to the extent permitted by law.

9. Contact Information
- For inquiries, please contact us at [Support Email].

By using the App, you acknowledge that you have read, understood, and agree to these Terms and Conditions.
    </string>
</resources>
